Mythica: The Darkspore is a action, adventure,
fantasy film directed by Anne K. Black.
Fighting through creature-infested lands and pursued by bounty hunters, Marek and her company are in a race
to recover all the shards of the Darkspore before it falls into the hands of an evil wizard.
Marek, played by Melanie Stone.
Thane, played by Adam Johnson.
Dagen, played by Jake Stormoen.
Teela, played by Nicola Posener.
Qole, played by Rocky Myers.
Hammerhead, played by Christopher Robin Miller.
Mythica is a series of primarily direct-to-video fantasy films.
The films are produced by Arrowstorm Entertainment, with first film Mythica: A Quest for
Heroes being partly funded by a Kickstarter campaign that collected $94,294.
There are six films in the Mythica series, all produced and
co-written by Jason Faller and Kynan Griffin.
The films star Melanie Stone as Marek, an escaped slave girl and budding magician, and co-star Kevin Sorbo as Gojun Pye the magician who trains
her, along with Adam Johnson, Jake Stormoen, and Nicola Posener as those that team up with Marek on various quests together.
The film explores themes of magic, sword, sorcery, necromancer, woman director.
The tone is dark.